Amin Ebrahimi

Email: amin.jemes@gmail.com

Phone: +98936-524-8382

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/amin347/

GitHub: github.com/amin347

Website: aiae.ir

Professional Summary

Highly skilled and motivated AI specialist with a Master's degree in Artificial Intelligence. Experienced in neural networks and deep learning, with a strong background in image processing projects. Additionally, I have two years of experience as a back-end developer at Hamta Rayaneh and Roshd, specializing in ASP.NET. Recently, at Glo3D, I have worked on several projects, including:

- Developing a video tour system that creates and integrates video and audio using user data and AI, with automated sharing on social media platforms.
- Adding reflection shadows under vehicles.
- Building a chatbot using the OpenAI engine and user data, with storage in vector databases.

Education

Master of Artificial Intelligence and Robotics

Khayyam University of Mashhad, Mashhad, Iran | September 2017 - September 2020

Dissertation: "Using Deep Learning in Stock Market Prediction"

GPA: 18.56/20

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Khayyam University of Mashhad, Mashhad, Iran | September 2012 - June 2017

GPA: 13.99/20

Professional Experience

Mid-level Python Developer

WebReed Inc., Nov 2022 - Present

- Developing a chatbot using Lang-chain, OpenAI, and Pinecone vector database.
- Working on virtual video tours using Python and OpenCV and After Effect.
- Building social video creation with auto-subtitling using OpenCV, Pillow, and OpenAI.

- Adding mirror-like shadow to car images using OpenCV.
- Capturing images from undercarriage cars using the slit-scan technique.
- Implementing YOLO 3.0 for object detection to remove license plates from images.
- Utilizing Python, OpenCV, and additional skills to enhance project outcomes.

Web Programmer

HamtaRayaneh, Sep 2017 - Jan 2018

• Employed Microsoft SQL Server, Entity Framework, and supplementary skills for web development projects.

Skills

- Programming Languages: Python, R, C#, C++
- AI/ML Frameworks: TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch, Scikit-learn
- Tools and Technologies: GCP, Vector-DBs, OpenCV, SOL, MATLAB
- $\hbox{-}\ Other\ Skills: Image\ Processing, Video\ Processing, Data\ Visualization, Natural\ Language\ Processing}$

Publications

[2017] S.H.Taheri, A.Ebrahimi, E.Emamjome, M.Adelkhani, SH.Hojati

"Using games in physiotherapist robot to improve brain performance." 4th National & 2nd International Conference on Applied Research in Electrical, Mechanical & Mechatronics Engineering Held by Malek-Ashtar University of Technology, Tehran, Iran.

This paper will be indexed in ISC(Proprietary code:9516071903) and CIVILICA data bases.

[2019] N.Javadi, A.Ebrahimi, S.H.Taheri

"Wood Wide Web(WWW) algorithm" 4th National Conference on Electrical and Computer Engineering Technology by Shahrood University of Technology, Tehran, Iran.

Proprietary code: etech2019-1155

Certifications

[2015] Robocup Iran Open 2015

Ynd Place [The Senior Demo League]

- Khayyam Physio Robot
- Use Robotics and Games in physical therapy

[2015] 3rd Khayyam Robotic Competitions

Ynd Place [The Senior Demo League]

- Khayyam Physio Robot
- Use Robotics and Games in physical therapy

[2015] ICRoM 2015

^τ rd Place [The Senior Demo League]

- Khayyam Physio Robot
- Use Robotics and Games in physical therapy

[2015] Robocup Iran Open 2015

Certificate of Participation [The Senior Demo League]

· Lobster Robot

[2017] Robocup Iran Open 2017

Certificate of Participation [The IRANOPENUAV League]

- VAIO Robotic Team
- Team Leader (Link)

[2015] ACM

Certificate of Participation [acm icpc sharif]

Languages

Persian - Mother tongue

English - B2 Level

References

- Sayed Hassan Taheri (Professor), Division of Mathematics and Computer [University of Khayyam], Email: h.taheri@khayyam.ac.ir, Phone: +985135156322
- Ali Jebreeli (Professor), Division of Computer [University of Khayyam], E-mail: a.jebreeli@khayyam.ac.ir, Phone: +985135156331